{"description":"Default","name":"Inference for Quantitative Data: Means","questions":[{"correct":0,"image_data":[],"options":["A paired t-test","A one sample t-interval for means","A linear regression t-interval for slope","Two sample t-interval for a difference between means"],"question":"A new smoothie shop has just recently opened in a town called Hillsdale. Although making sales the smoothie shop owners hired a marketing team to launch an advertising campaign to the locals. Which of the following inference procedures would be best to see if there is a difference in sales before and after the campaign?"},{"correct":3,"image_data":[],"options":["1.333","1.337","1.740","1.746"],"question":"What is the critical t* for a 90% confidence interval from a sample of size n = 17?"},{"correct":0,"image_data":[],"options":["(16.467, 29.867)","(17.040, 29.359)","(17.609, 28.791)","(17.978, 28.422)"],"question":"A factory that produces potato chips wants to find the average number of chips per snack size bag that it produces. Randomly selecting 6 from the manufacturer the following: 19, 28, 23, 24, 27, 18. Using this data assuming all conditions are met construct a 99% confidence interval for the mean number of chips per bag."},{"correct":1,"image_data":[],"options":["Margin of error decreases as sample size increases given the confidence interval and sample standard deviation were the same.","Margin of error is proportional to 1/sqrt(n)","Margin of error does account for bias and doesn’t account for sampling variability",""],"question":"Which of the following is NOT true about the margin of error?\nMargin of error decreases as sample size increases given the confidence interval and sample standard deviation were the same."},{"correct":1,"image_data":[],"options":["Decreasing the confidence level","Decreasing the sample size to 5","Increasing the sample size to 15","Increasing the variability of state capitals known"],"question":"A geography teacher wants to estimate the average number of state capitals between two of their classes. The teacher randomly selects 10 students from each of his classes. Which of the following would increase the precision of estimate?"},{"correct":2,"image_data":[],"options":["The average battery life has not changed.","The average battery life has increased.","The battery life has decreased.","The new product will have no effect on the battery life."],"question":"A new tech company claims that their new product increases the average battery life more than other competitors. A hypothesis test is conducted to evaluate this claim. Which of the following is the appropriate alternative hypothesis for this scenario?"},{"correct":1,"image_data":[],"options":["Paired T-test","One sample T-test","Two sample T-test","Two tailed T-test"],"question":"A student wants to figure out if there is a significant difference between the price of the same textbooks from two different bookstores. The prices of two randomly sampled books from each bookstore were compared. Which hypothesis test should be conducted?"},{"correct":0,"image_data":[],"options":["We reject the null hypothesis, there is evidence to support the student's claim of a significant difference in wait times between boardwalks in the east and west coast.","We reject the null hypothesis, there is no significant evidence to support the student’s claim of a significant difference in wait time between boardwalks in the east and west coast.","We reject the alternative hypothesis, there is evidence to support the student's claim of a significant difference in wait times between boardwalks in the east and west coast","We reject the alternative hypothesis, there is no significant evidence to support the student’s claim of a significant difference in wait time between boardwalks in the east and west coast."],"question":"A student wants to find out if there is a significant difference in wait times at carnival games at different boardwalks. Randomly sampled 14 average in the west coast on average 7.96 minutes with a standard deviation of 1.87, while randomly sampled 22 in the east coast on average 6.38 minutes with a standard deviation of 1.24. The student believes that there is a significant difference between the wait time between boardwalks. Is there evidence to support the student’s claim?"},{"correct":3,"image_data":[],"options":["Estimating true difference between salaries of employees working in different industries.","Analyzing the average rainfall between different major cities over a year.","Comparing average IQ scores between countries in Asia and Europe.","Testing the effectiveness of a new pain relief medication for migraine patients."],"question":"Which of the following involves paired data?"},{"correct":2,"image_data":[],"options":["- 1.36","- 0.43","0.43","1.36"],"question":"On average there are about 17 unpopped kernels in a popcorn bag for a specific manufacturer. Based on a random sample of 55 popcorn bags a 90% confidence interval for the true mean of unpopped kernels is (15.29, 18.01). Assuming all conditions have been met, which of the following is the correct test statistic?"}]}
